<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robert Ayers</title>
    <description>My personal blog/resume.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 22:02:26 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 22:02:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Difficulty of the First Address</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Doctor Johnson stands in my estimation at the pinnacle of moral thought.  The world remembers him as a writer of dictionaries, poet and wit.  When he is quoted it is usually in a context far removed from his own.  Many on the Internet copy and paste quotes in a hurried pace, without noticing the source.  My favorite instance is when I noticed Henry Adams quote in praise of teachers pasted over a pretty picture.  Adams’s seldom intended to inspire with his writing.  I stand guilty guilty of this as much as anyone else.  A quick Google search leads to me quotes learned and wise and I pilfer them without much regard their author’s original intent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Samuel Johnson is best taken at his word.  The reason I decided to read all of The Rambler on the corresponding dates of publication, is to surrender myself to  Johnson’s context and perhaps attain his true intention.  I want him to mold my point of view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The essays of the Rambler were written two week and appeared on Tuesday and Saturday.  Even if you can’t resist the comparison of a blog the depth of content will soon convince you otherwise. Perhaps the eighteenth century mind could consume depth better than the twenty-first or, more likely, Doctor Johnson never had a little thought in is life.  You could consume these essays the way we do blog posts but then you would probably miss the point.  The reason we can still walk into a library or bookstore and see these essays on the shelf is because they defy consumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me give an example:  The first entry is about beginnings.  He considers the ways in which society inaugurates undertaking of different sorts other than writing.  There is no accepted ceremony&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2016/03/24/difficulty-starting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2016/03/24/difficulty-starting.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pardon my dust</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have started to build this site with Jekyll and there is a bit of a learning curve.  First, I want to push myself to learn Markdown, which doesn’t seem to be too lofty a goal.  Markdown is intended to save time.  So, I consider it worth the effort to learn it.  Second, jekyll has a lot of cool tools that I need to wrap my head around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an apprentice developer at Nashville Software School I’ve learned a lot in 4 months and I am eager to stretch my mind and expand my skill set.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2016/01/12/figuring-things-out.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2016/01/12/figuring-things-out.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
